(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T22:59:08.133055",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
えー 皆様
Um, everyone...
本日は 轟はじめ生誕祭2026
Welcome to Todoroki Hajime Birthday Live 2026,
「Rise in motion」にお越しくださいまして
"Rise in motion"!
誠にありがとうございます！
Thank you all so much for coming!
えー 開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます
Before we begin, I have a few announcements and requests for you all.
えー 当配信は一部収録を含みますが、生配信部分もございますので
While parts of this stream are pre-recorded, there are live portions as well,
いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてください！
so please flood the chat with comments and hype things up!
今もね、じわーっていっぱい「おー」「こんにちは」「きちゃ」「パチパチ」と ありがとうございます！
I already see so many coming in—"Oh," "Hello," "It's here," clapping... Thank you!
えー 当配信のハッシュタグは #轟はじめ生誕祭2026 です
The hashtag for this stream is #轟はじめ生誕祭2026.
SNSでたくさんポストしていただけると嬉しいです
I'd be so happy if you could post about it on social media!
えー 開演中はね、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影大歓迎ですので
During the show, taking photos with your camera or smartphone is super welcome,
たくさんポストして盛り上げていただけると幸いです
so please post lots of screenshots and help hype it up!
えー それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください
Now then, please sit tight and wait just a moment until the show starts!
えー 皆様
Um, everyone!
本日は 轟はじめ生誕祭2026
Welcome to Todoroki Hajime Birthday Live 2026,
「Rise in motion」にお越しくださいまして
"Rise in motion"!
誠にありがとうございます！ パート2！
Thank you so much for coming! Part 2!
どうでしょうか？ なんか... ゴトゴトしてなさそうですね、皆様？
How is it looking? It doesn't seem to be glitching, right, everyone?
「うおー」って、「わくわく」「こんにちは」と... 大丈夫そうです！
I see "Woah," "Excited," "Hello"... Looks like we're good to go!
えー 開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を... ちょっともう1回申し上げます
Before we start, let me repeat the announcements and requests one more time!
えー 当配信は一部収録を
This stream includes some pre-recorded segments,
含みますが
however,
生配信部分もございますので
there are also live portions,
いっぱいコメントして盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです
so I'd be happy if you'd leave lots of comments and hype it up!
きちゃー！大丈夫ー？パート2！きちゃー！ありがとうー！
Here we go! Are you doing okay? Part 2! Here we go! Thank you!
配信のハッシュタグは #おはしの生誕祭2026 です！
The hashtag for this stream is #OhashiBirthday2026!
SNSでたくさんポストしてください！
Please post a lot on social media!
公演中はカメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影大歓迎です！
Taking photos with cameras or smartphones during the show is welcome!
たくさんポストして盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです！
We'd love it if you post a lot and build up the excitement!
それでは、開演まで今しばらくお待ちください！
Now then, please wait a little longer until the show begins!
バンザイ無能な命に
Banzai to a useless life,
くだらないよまがい物だってばラリアッチュー
it's nonsense, a total knockoff, Lariat-chu!
偶然息してるようなもん
It's like I'm breathing just by chance,
不条理浴びながら僕らは HOME
getting showered in absurdity, we're HOME.
才能はゼロ どうにかしてしまっちゃってるけど
Zero talent, somehow I'm making it work though.
歓声は NO だって虚ノー
The cheers are NO, because empty NO.
愛にもたれた言葉で心拍数
Heart rate raised by words leaning on love,
生きてく程胸は沈んでゆく
the more I live, the deeper my heart sinks.
どうなってんだろな この音が揺れるの
What's going on, I wonder? Will this sound shake
かいつまんでもしょうがねえ
Even if I sum it up, it can't be helped.
汗かき稼ぐお金はどんだけ？
How much money do I make sweating it out?
あーだこーだそんなもんか 五月蠅いわな
Blah blah, is that all it is? How annoying.
バンザイ無能な命に
Banzai to a useless life,
から回っていく脳を満たしてくれ
fill up my brain that's spinning out of control.
未来予想図なんか描けない
I can't draw any vision of the future.
くだらないよまがい物だってそれ
It's nonsense, that's just a knockoff too.
半端者ならやれない nutty tune
A half-baked person can't handle this nutty tune.
お赤い色になって僕は思い通り
Turning a deep crimson, I get my way.
太陽系で踊った 罵詈雑言インベーダー
Danced in the solar system, abusive invader.
足が止まってるシューゲイザー 死にそうでもギリですか？
Shoegazer standing frozen, even if you're dying, is it barely enough?
のらりくらりかわすわ 初めまして神様
Dodging lazily, nice to meet you, God.
もし救われるのなら 腹切るわ今から
If I can be saved, I'll slice my stomach right now.
あー GET DOWN GET DOWN 揺らめく
Ah, GET DOWN, GET DOWN, swaying,
GET DOWN GET DOWN 飲み込んだ清濁が
GET DOWN, GET DOWN, the good and bad swallowed whole
君を狂わせてんだ
is driving you crazy.
めったなもんじゃ驚かねえ
I won't be surprised by just anything,
汗かき生きた最期もあっけねえ
the end of a life lived sweating it out is anticlimactic too.
なんだかんだそんなもんさ 虚しいわな
All in all, that's just how it is. How empty.
虚しいわな
How empty.
絵の具で
With paint,
からまわっていく
spinning out of control,
脳を乱してくれ
mess up my mind.
未来の図なんか書けない
I can't draw any plan for the future.
くだらない 歪みの呪いだってそれ
It's just a foolish, twisted curse.
半端ものなら やれない 毎日
You can't make it through daily life if you're half-hearted.
お互いロストして 僕は思う
As we both get lost, I think to myself...
ええじゃないか
[Eejanaika]
パラリラ ここはきっと奈落だ
Pararira, this must be the abyss.
声にもならぬ声が
A voice that can't even become words
腹の底から競り上がるんだ
surges up from deep in my gut.
だからそれ 押し倒す本能
So push it down, that instinct!
ゆらゆら 煮え湯の海から
Swaying, from a sea of boiling water,
いらっしゃいと 誘う鬼ヶ島
Onigashima beckons, "Welcome!"
ただただ 君は呟くんだ
You just whisper,
人は 怖いねと
"People are scary, aren't they?"
今 はじける七色
Now, seven colors burst forth!
ハイハイハイハイ 中央へ行って
Yeah yeah yeah yeah, head to the center
踊り散らすの
and dance like crazy!
ファッションビートに気取って
Posing to the fashion beat,
陰キャな狂人物じゃない
I'm no introverted lunatic.
報われない悲しみ喰らっていこう
Let's devour this unrequited sadness!
ファッションビートに染まって
Steeped in the fashion beat,
言うことないなら息してても
if you've got nothing to say, breathing is
無駄だ
useless!
ハイハイハイハイ 愛情・執念よ
Yeah yeah yeah yeah, affection and tenacity!
ええじゃないか ええじゃないか
Isn't it great? Isn't it fine?
この先は何も分からんし
We don't know what lies ahead anyway!
ええじゃないか ええじゃないか
Isn't it great? Isn't it fine?
クソタレ 見て慣れ 日本の...
You bastard, get used to watching Japan's...
はー 晴れくる世の中から
Haa, from a brightening world,
ハイハイハイハイ 中央へ行って
Yeah yeah yeah yeah, head to the center
終わりにすんな
and don't end it here!
ファッションビートに気取って
Posing to the fashion beat,
陰キャな狂人物じゃない
I'm no introverted lunatic.
報われない悲しみ喰らっていこう
Let's devour this unrequited sadness!
ファッションビートに染まって
Steeped in the fashion beat,
言うことないなら息してても
if you've got nothing to say, breathing is
無駄だ
useless!
ハイハイハイハイ 愛情・執念よ
Yeah yeah yeah yeah, affection and tenacity!
絵に描いたようなストーリー
A picture-perfect story,
僕の色
my color.
濡れるほどに
So deeply soaked,
落ち込んでた
I was feeling down.
モノクロに過ぎる日は
If I can overcome the days
乗り越えられたら
passing in monochrome...
あぁ 今夜は笑って
Ah, laugh tonight,
あの幽霊船にキスをして
kiss that ghost ship,
七色に生まれ変わるのさ
and be reborn in seven colors!
ファッションビートに染まって
Steeped in the fashion beat,
言うことないなら息してても
if you've got nothing to say, breathing is
無駄だ
useless!
ハイハイハイハイ 愛情・執念よ
Yeah yeah yeah yeah, affection and tenacity!
うわぁ〜！ たのち〜！
Woah~! That was so fun~!
やっぱ歌って踊るのたのち〜！
Singing and dancing really is so much fun~!
イェ〜イ！
Yay~!
いやぁ〜 ちょっとぶつかっちゃったの ごめんちゃ
Man~ I bumped into you guys a bit, sorry about that!
え？ なんかダンスとかやってたんすか？
Huh? Were you guys doing some dance routine or something?
お？ なん、なんつった？
Oh? What, what did you say?
え、なんか撮ってました？
Wait, were you recording something?
え、なんか撮ってましたよね？
Wait, you were recording this, right?
え、てか、これ配信されてます、これ？！
Wait, like, is this live streaming right now?!
えぇ？！ ちょ、ちょっと待って！
Ehh?! W-Wait a minute!
なんかコメントが超流れてるんですけど
The comments are scrolling so fast...
反転してて読めません！
They're flipped, so I can't read them!
なんか、パチパチって拍手してくれてて
Um, people are clapping for me...
なんか「カッコよすぎ」って... 何や？
Something like "too cool"... wait, what?
すごい、なんか... 草生やされた
Wow... they're spamming "kusa" (lol)...
なんか、ありがとうございます
Um, thank you so much!
ハッシュタグ「音一しの生誕祭2026」って
The hashtag #OtozoHajimeBirthday2026...
なんかたくさんポチッとしてくれてるみたいなんですけど
It seems like a lot of people are posting with it...
なんだろ、このタグは？分かんないけど
What is this tag? I don't know, but...
初め祝ってもらってるし、ポチッとしてもらったらお礼言わんと
Since everyone's celebrating Hajime, I should thank them for posting!
有難う
Thank you!
いや、初め、歌ったり踊ったりとかするの好きで
Well, Hajime loves singing and dancing,
本当はたくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることに憧れて
and I've always longed to perform in front of lots of people,
ちょっと上京したいな、とか思ってるんですけど
so I've been thinking about moving to Tokyo,
ちょっと勇気が出なくて...
but I just haven't had the courage...
え？
Huh?
「初めなら大丈夫」？「行ける」？
"Hajime can do it"? "You can go"?
コメントの方はちょっとどう思ってる？
What do the people in the comments think?
「可愛い」なんて... あれ？
They're saying "Cute"... wait?
ダンス上手い！すごい褒められてる！かっこいい！褒められてる！
"Great dancing!" I'm getting praised! "Cool!" More praise!
よーし！じゃあ皆さんにすごい勇気をもらったので、初め...
Alright! You guys gave me so much courage, so Hajime...
行ってきます！夢を目指して上京してくる！
is going! I'm moving to Tokyo to chase my dream!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
荒れ狂う季節の中を 2人は1人きり さらり
In the raging seasons, the two of us are all alone, easily
明け行く夕日の中を 今夜も昼下がり さらり
In the dawning sunset, tonight is early afternoon, easily
どれほど朽ち果てようと 最後にゃ笑いたい
No matter how much it decays, I want to have the last laugh
何のために戦おうとも 動機は愛がいい
No matter what you fight for, your motivation should be love
新しい日々は 探さずとも常にここに
Even if you don't look for new days, they are always here
色々見てきたけれど この瞳は永遠にきらり
I've seen many things, but these eyes of mine are forever shining
あれほど生きてきたけど 全ては夢みたい
I've lived so much, but everything is like a dream
あれもこれも魅力的ながら 私は君がいい
This and that are attractive, but I want you
どこにいたの 探してたよ
Where'd you go? I searched for you
連れてって 連れてって
Take me with you, take me with you
何もかも 捨ててくよ
I'll abandon everything
どこまでも どこまでも
Anywhere, anywhere
荒れ狂う季節の中も 群衆の中も
In the raging seasons, in the crowd
君とならば さらり さらり
With you, so easily, so easily
新しい日々も 拙い過去も 全てがきらり
New days and a shoddy past are all shining
無くしてしまったものを 振り返って ほろり
Reflect on what you've lost, sentimental
時には途方に暮れて ただ風に吹かれて ゆらり
At times at a loss, blowin' in the wind, swaying
息せき切ってきたの 行き先は決めたの
I was out of breath / I've decided my future
迷わずにいきたいけど 保証はしないよ
I wanna go without hesitating, but I can't make any guarantees
どこへ行こうかって　本当に迷った
Wondering where to go, I was really lost.
新しい日々は　探さずとも常にここに
New days are always right here without even looking.
ここに　ここに　ここに
Right here, right here, right here.
ああ　いろいろ見てきたけれど
Ah, I've seen all kinds of things, but...
この瞳は永遠にきらり
...these eyes sparkle forever.
ああ　生きてきたけれど　全ては夢みたい
Ah, I've lived through it all, but it all feels like a dream.
誰も彼も魅力的だけど　私は君がいい
Everyone is attractive, but I prefer you.
どこに行ってたの　探していたよ
Where had you gone? I was looking for you.
連れてって　連れてって
Take me with you, take me with you.
何もかも捨ててくよ
I'll leave everything behind.
どこまでも　どこまでも
Anywhere, everywhere.
荒れ狂う季節の中も　群衆の中も
Through raging seasons and through crowds of people,
君とならば　さらり　さらり
with you, it's smooth and light.
新しい日々も
The new days,
拙い過去も
and the clumsy past,
全てがきらり
everything shines brightly.
いいよじゃあほら
Fine then, come on,
踊れば
if you dance,
幕開けの合図が
the signal for the curtain call...
It's coming back
月火から水木金お疲れ Everybody clap your hands
From Mon-Tue to Wed-Thu-Fri, good work! Everybody clap your hands!
待ちわびた華金に It's time to come out with your friends
On the long-awaited TGIF, it's time to come out with your friends!
世間はワクワク　目線は遠く　心も体もボロボロです
The world is excited, looking far away, my mind and body are worn out.
頑張り屋の日本人 Everybody clap your hands
To all the hard-working Japanese people, everybody clap your hands!
やり切れない朝に　ため息ついちゃって
Sighing on an unbearable morning,
何ともないルーティン　染み込ませて
soaking in a routine that feels like nothing...
否定した自分のせい？　憧れ持ったの定義？
Is it my fault for denying it? What's the definition of longing?
結局はいつも通りさ
In the end, it's business as usual.
過ぎ去っていく Day by day
Passing by, day by day,
考えたって No best right way
even if I think about it, there's no best right way.
不格好なストーリーにして Let's fly away
Turn it into an awkward story and let's fly away!
Welcome to our theater ほら
Welcome to our theater, look!
踊れば
If you dance,
幕開けの合図が It's coming back
the signal for the curtain call, it's coming back!
波瀾万丈な人生くらいが　ちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just right!
君が作る Showtime
The showtime you create,
見せて　見せて頂戴
show me, please show me!
春夏秋冬にアレコレ Everybody clap your hands
Spring, summer, autumn, winter, through it all, everybody clap your hands!
ギリギリ駆け込んで間に合う Never ending game
Barely rushing in on time, a never-ending game.
気持ちは GO GO されども SLOW SLOW　現実そう甘くないね
Feeling ready to GO GO, but going SLOW SLOW, reality isn't that sweet, is it?
働き者の日本人 Everybody clap your hands
To the hard-working Japanese people, everybody clap your hands!
お決まりのスタンスで
With the usual stance,
How can I be myself, am I?
どれもこれも色のない世界に　興味ない
I have no interest in this colorless world, any of it.
We don't know where we gotta go
Welcome to our theater ほら
Welcome to our theater, look!
踊れば
If you dance,
幕開けの合図が It's coming back
the signal for the curtain call, it's coming back!
波瀾万丈な人生くらいが　ちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just right!
君が作る Showtime
The showtime you create,
見せて　見せて
show me, show me...
過ぎ去っていく Day by day
Passing by, day by day,
考えたって No best right way
even if I think about it, there's no best right way.
不格好なストーリーにして Let's run away
Make it an awkward story and let's run away!
Welcome to our theater ほら
Welcome to our theater, look!
踊れば
If you dance,
幕開けの合図が It's coming back
the signal for the curtain call, it's coming back!
波瀾万丈な人生くらいが　ちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just right!
君が作る Showtime
The showtime you create,
見せて　見せて頂戴
show me, please show me!
とびきり Showtime　誰でも Showtime
Exceptional showtime, anyone's showtime!
あなたの Showtime　見せて頂戴
Your showtime, please show me!
とびきり Showtime　誰でも Showtime
Exceptional showtime, anyone's showtime!
あなたの Showtime　見せて頂戴
Your showtime, please show me!
えっ、あの... 星街すいせいちゃんでしょうか？
Um, excuse me... are you Hoshimachi Suisei-chan?
ご存知かしら？ありがとう！
Ah, you know who I am? Thank you!
えっ、あの、なんか... 超強引に出てたけど...
Eh, um, like... you came on super forcefully, but...
一緒に歌えて嬉しかったりーしゅ！
I was so happy we could sing together-rishu!
私も嬉しかったわ
I was happy too.
わー！嬉しかった、楽しかった！ありがとう
Yay! I was so happy, it was fun! Thank you.
え、でも、このシアター勝手に入っていいんですか？
Eh, but is it okay for us to just enter this theater?
まあ、ダメかもしれないわね
Well, it might not be allowed.
ダメなん！？
It's not allowed!?
え？じゃあ怒られるとこ？
Eh? Then are we gonna get scolded?
まあ、怒られるわ
Well, we'll definitely get scolded.
な、なんでここ連れてきてくれたんですか？
Wh-Why did you bring me here then?
あそこの人がもう銃構えてるわ、こうやって
That person over there is already aiming a gun like this.
怖い、怖い！
Scary, scary!
え、そんな物騒な場所なんですか？
Eh, is this place really that dangerous?
あ、違うの。あの人、オーディション出場者で
Ah, no. That person is an audition participant.
オーディションやってるの。出場者さん、オーディション。ね？
They're holding auditions. An audition participant. Right?
ここでオーディションやってるんだ！
So they're holding auditions here!
そうだよ。受けた方がいいんじゃない？ね？
That's right. Shouldn't you take it too? Right?
じゃないと撃たれる。撃たれる
Otherwise you'll get shot. You'll get shot.
怖い、怖いよー！撃たれるよ！
Scary, scary! You'll get shot!
あれ、街街すいせいじゃない！？
Wait, isn't that Hoshimachi Suisei!?
いけね！じゃあね！
Oh crap! See ya!
え！？ちょっと、すいちゃんやばい！
Eh!? Wait, Sui-chan, oh no!
あれれ？どっちや...
Huh? Which way...
シュッ...
Shh...
Step like 奪い取りに Party party jam
Step like taking it by force, party party jam
抜き足 差し足 あら行く手は劇場
Stealthy steps, tiptoeing, oh, my destination is the theater
Step by stepping night 教えるわ
Step by stepping night, let me show you
本能の思うまま踊らせて
Let me dance just as my instincts guide me
強気の決意隠して 少しニヤッと笑って
Hiding my bold resolve, smirking just a bit
高気まり蹴り上げ シズカニちょっと痛感させる
Kicking up my spirits, quietly making them feel the sting
仕留めてあげるわ
I'll finish you off
Step like 同じダンスじゃ 冗談じゃない
Step like the same old dance? You've got to be joking
Spin off もう一人の自分に勝つの
Spin off, I'll beat this other version of myself
だって 盗まれたら取り返すのが基本だ
After all, if it's stolen, taking it back is the basic rule
あいつ達 シズカニ足音
Those guys, quiet footsteps
ひらりと交わして目の前
Lightly dodging, right before your eyes
さらりと手には挑戦状
Smoothly holding a challenge letter in hand
華麗に無音一撃
A splendid, silent single strike
シズカニちょっと痛感させる 仕留めてあげるわ
Quietly making them feel the sting, I'll finish you off
Step like 奪い返し Party party jam
Step like taking it back, party party jam
抜き足 差し足 あら行く手は劇場
Stealthy steps, tiptoeing, oh, my destination is the theater
Step by stepping night そのまま踊るわ
Step by stepping night, I'll keep dancing just like this
譲り合っていてはダメ 踏み出してみてよ
You shouldn't compromise—take a step forward
ここで決めるの 誰も奪えやしないわ
I'll decide it here, no one can steal it away
胸に秘めてる宝石と
With the gem hidden in my heart
静かに踊った 静かに踊ってよ
Danced quietly, dance quietly now
ステップはお静かに
Keep your steps quiet
Switch it 散々に目立って Jack 浮かぶ影がカンカン Top-Secret ガランド...
Switch it, standing out wildly, Jack, floating shadow ding-dong, Top-Secret, hollow...
ちょっとお洒落な帽子とステッキでナビゲート
Navigating with a stylish hat and cane.
絶品最高なルナティック 既に今宵主役はグラビティソー
Exquisite, supreme lunatic, the star tonight is already Gravity So.
さあ乾杯してキャバレー 今はこの欲望に溺れよ
Cheers to the cabaret, let's drown in this desire tonight.
有限なら夜が明ける前まで
If time is limited, then until the night breaks...
味わい尽くすべき
...we should savor every last drop.
You are Bad Hatter 支配なるモンスター
You are Bad Hatter, a controlling monster.
We are Bad Hatter 目線も罪状もナンセンス
We are Bad Hatter, gaze and charges are all nonsense.
Bang bang Moonlight 渋滞のダンスフロア
Bang bang Moonlight, a crowded dance floor.
We are stakeholder 狂騒に呑まれ踊れ
We are stakeholders, swallow the frenzy and dance!
ラチあかぬアビエーション つまり空中飛び交う狂言ド
Endless aviation, farces flying through the air.
会場内なら平等さ 老いも若きもバカしか語り合わぬ
Inside the venue, all are equal; young and old, only fools chatter here.
絶品最高なルナティック 誰も彼もが耳打ち狂言トーク
Exquisite, supreme lunatic, everyone whispering wild stories.
一緒にどうデスお嬢さん 素直はやした紳士が Shall we dance?
How about joining us, lady? A gentleman says, "Shall we dance?"
有名無名とかどんな見た目だろうが
Whether famous or unknown, whatever you look like...
気にする暇もない
...there's no time to care!
You are Bad Hatter 支配なるモンスター
You are Bad Hatter, a controlling monster.
We are Bad Hatter 目線も罪状もナンセンス
We are Bad Hatter, gaze and charges are all nonsense.
Bang bang Moonlight 渋滞のダンスフロア
Bang bang Moonlight, a crowded dance floor.
We are stakeholder 狂騒に呑まれ踊れ
We are stakeholders, swallow the frenzy and dance!
You are Bad Hatter 支配なるモンスター
You are Bad Hatter, a controlling monster.
We are Bad Hatter 目線も罪状もナンセンス
We are Bad Hatter, gaze and charges are all nonsense.
Bang bang Moonlight 渋滞のダンスフロア
Bang bang Moonlight, a crowded dance floor.
We are stakeholder 狂騒に呑まれ踊れ
We are stakeholders, swallow the frenzy and dance!
うわ！お前ちゃっきーをやってる！
Whoa! You're playing Jacky!
何持っとるの？
What are you holding?
バツ？
An X mark?
バツってどういうこと？あ、もしかして終わりちゃんの判定だったの？
What do you mean, X? Oh, was that Owari-chan's verdict?
え、だってさっきなんかノリノリでやってたじゃん！
Wait, but you were getting totally into it just now!
え、出てけって？なんだよ！
Huh? "Get out"? What the heck!
はじめ頑張って、ちょっと、ちょっと手伝って！
Hajime, do something! Help me out here!
ねぇ！
Hey!
あれ？なんか、う、動かないんだけど！
Huh? Wait... she's not moving at all!
はー...なんか話し掛けてもダメみたいだ...
Sigh... Guess it's no use talking to her...
なんだよ、こっちから願い下げだ！こんな劇場出てってやる！
Whatever, I don't need this! I'm leaving this theater!
ちくしょう！調子乗りやがって！
Damn it! Getting so full of herself!
何見てんだよ！
What are you looking at?!
見てんじゃねぇ！ちっ！
Stop staring! Tch!
うわぁぁ...くそ...
Ughhh... Damn it...
脳線チュウ ONLINE 脳天気トウガシテイレ
Brainlines connected ONLINE, carefree and singing aloud...
不適切トシテ キリノナイテイセイ レ
Endless corrections for being "inappropriate"...
正義シハンダイ ミスターX ホウガシテイレ
Justice pedestal, Mr. X spreading rumors...
真偽不明ナンテ 正気ジャナイ
Calling truth unverified is insane!
夜はオン・ナナ・ナ・ノ
The night goes on, na na na...
僕らオン・ナナ・ナ・デ
We go on, na na na...
平穏な協調 何言わんや 混線場 吸って吐いて Judgement
Peaceful harmony? In this chaos, breathe in, breathe out, Judgment!
今夜決着 無礼講 結構デス
Settling it tonight, let your hair down, that's fine!
目良様 ナンセンス 花々 ナンセンス
Mera-sama, nonsense! Spectacular nonsense!
イケル ナガレ 黙れ 黙れ
Go with the flow, shut up, shut up!
この世は ナンセンス 誠に ギンダス
This world is nonsense, truly shameless!
義の毒ね 哀れ 哀れ 叱れ
Poisonous righteousness, pitiful, scold it!
ほら 盛衰 際立つ 一層 チャージ エラーに よろしく 言っといて
Rise and fall stands out even more, charge ahead, say hi to the error!
まさに宣言通り Dirty party night
Exactly as declared, dirty party night!
右も左も Don't cry
Left or right, don't cry!
ふと沸いた Checkmate
A sudden checkmate.
ようやく今晩 Break の結果です
Tonight at last, here are the break results!
皆様ナンセンス 甚だナンセンス 切る流れ
Everyone, it's nonsense, utter nonsense, cut the flow!
溜まれ 溜まれ
Accumulate, accumulate!
この世はナンセンス 誠に感です
This world is nonsense, truly a gut feeling.
気の毒ね 雨れ 雨れ
How pitiful, rain down, rain down!
Can you understand?
Yeah yeah, yeah yeah
皆様ナンセンス 甚だナンセンス 切る流れ
Everyone, it's nonsense, utter nonsense, cut the flow!
溜まれ 溜まれ
Accumulate, accumulate!
この世はナンセンス 花からナンセンス 切る流れ
This world is nonsense, nonsense from the start, cut the flow!
溜まれ 溜まれ
Accumulate, accumulate!
間もなく感です 誠に感です
Shortly it's a feeling, truly a feeling.
氣は済んだ？ 下がれ 下がれ 下がれ
Satisfied now? Step back, step back, step back!
ほら正解気取っていらっしゃい
Go on, pretend you've got the right answer.
期待生じちゃっていいから
It's fine to build up expectations!
Rest in peace ご冥福を んで来世で会おうか See you again
Rest in peace, my condolences, let me see you in the next life, see you again!
ちょっ、危な！ 危ないんじゃないですかー！
Whoa, watch out! Isn't that dangerous?!
は？ 何チョロチョロ動いて？ お前、ダンサーか？
Huh? What are you slinking around for? Are you a dancer?
え？ ダンサーですけど...
Eh? I am a dancer, though...
へぇー、私達も... ダンサーでーす！
Oh? We are... dancers too!
え、なーんか凄いダンサーがいっぱい出てきた！
Huh, a whole bunch of awesome dancers just showed up!
なんかさ、初めて来たダンスのオーディション落ちちゃってさ...
You know, I just failed my very first dance audition...
もしかして、あそこのシアターですか？
Could it be that theater over there?
え、そう！ それ私達も落ちました！
Yeah, that one! We failed that one too!
私も！ 私も！ みんな落ちた仲間ー！？
Me too! Me too! We're all failed audition buddies?!
あのミニバン長身審査員、センスねぇよな！
That tall judge with the minivan has zero sense!
ウチらのダンス、ちゃんと見せつけてやろうじゃん！
Let's show them what our dancing is really made of!
もう壁とは踊らないぞ！ イサキ・リオナ！
I won't dance facing a wall anymore! Isaki Riona!
3メートルの覇気、水見亜生！
3 meters of presence, Mizumi Aso!
カオスに落ちる、ハコス・ベールズ！
Falling into chaos, Hakos Baelz!
宇宙一の番長になる、轟はじめ！
Becoming the number one boss in the universe, Todoroki Hajime!
ウチらの始まりは... こっからー！
Our start begins... right here!
え、皆さん！ こっからー！
Hey everyone! From here!
Hey boy 平凡に born in the ニッポン 産声オギャー 行く先は荒野
Hey boy, born ordinary in Japan, a newborn's cry "ogyaa", heading into the wilderness!
ノーマル以下が如何にして 地下深く眠る鉱脈掘れますか？
How can someone below average dig up ore veins buried deep underground?
知るか！ 伸るか反るかしかねぇ この世の中
Who cares! It's sink or swim in this world!
確かな価値観など無価値か
Are firm values useless here?
カットなったってこの葛藤で生まれた Take は Cut できん yo
Even if you get pissed, the take born from this conflict can't be cut, yo!
I can't be someone else, oh I know, I know...
このブレーキを壊したいの したいの
I want to break this brake, I really do!
これだけじゃやれねぇってわかってる
I know I can't pull it off with just this.
でもこれしかねぇからこれにかかってる
But since this is all I've got, everything rides on it.
間違ってる未来でも俺には光ってる
Even if it's a mistaken future, it shines brightly to me!
Let it fire!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子 ぶち壊しようもないままが
Burning this fighting spirit, breaking those iron bars, staying helpless as I am...
自分なんだ こっから始まんだ
...that's who I am, it all starts from here!
いつかの童心もって努力し 夢と相思相愛になれるはずなんだ
Working hard with childhood passion, I should be able to fall in love with my dreams.
こっから こっから始まんだ
From here, it starts right here!
1 2 3 4 順番通り
One, two, three, four, in order!
行ってないだけで予定通り
Things haven't gone smoothly, but it's still as planned.
ローリン ローリン 転がっていけ
Rollin', rollin', keep on rolling!
よりどりみどりの一生
A life full of endless choices!
1 2 3 4 順番通り
One, two, three, four, in order!
行ってないだけで予定通り
Things haven't gone smoothly, but it's still as planned.
ローリン ローリン 転がっていけ yo
Rollin', rollin', keep on rolling, yo!
こっから始まんだ
It starts right here!
こっから？ どっから？ わからん だって燃料自体はすっからかん
From here? From where? Who knows, since the fuel tank is completely empty!
こらアカンわ 楽観し簡単にとりあえずまさに難関
Oh man, this is bad, trying to be optimistic about a total hurdle!
一人になりたくても人だらけ さらけ出すにも一苦労なわけ
Even if I want to be alone, it's crowded, laying it all bare is a total struggle.
聞かれたくないサイレン ピーポーピーポーピーポー
Sirens I don't want to hear, wee-woo wee-woo wee-woo!
黄色信号でずっと進行
Moving forward constantly on yellow lights.
辛抱した先は歩こうぜレッドカーペット
Beyond all this patience, let's walk the red carpet!
タリラリラリラッタ come on!
Ta-ri-ra-ri-ra-ri-rat-ta, come on!
よりどりみどりってさっき言ったろ？
Didn't I tell you earlier it's full of choices?
明日ありと思う心の仇桜
Thinking tomorrow will come is like counting on fickle cherry blossoms.
生きてることが青天の霹靂
Just being alive feels like a bolt from the blue!
しかし悔しさで黒く燃える腹の中
Yet inside, frustration burns black and fierce!
燃やせ 燃やせ 燃やせ
Burn it, burn it, burn it up!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子 ぶち壊しようもないままが
Burning this fighting spirit, breaking those iron bars, staying helpless as I am...
自分なんだ こっから始まんだ
...that's who I am, it all starts from here!
いつかの童心もって努力し 夢と相思相愛になれるはずなんだ
Working hard with childhood passion, I should be able to fall in love with my dreams.
こっから こっから始まんだ
From here, it starts right here!
One, two, three, let's go!
俺 悪くない 何も間違ってない
I'm not in the wrong, I haven't done anything wrong
自分じゃない 何かのせいにしたい
I want to blame it on something that isn't me
天才じゃないの痛感せえ 分かりなさい
Realize acutely that you're no genius, get it through your head
これフィクションじゃない よく見なさい
This isn't fiction, take a good look
天賦の才などない でも
I have no natural talent, but...
やめられない 未才
I can't quit, still unpolished
あたしゃアホか 馬鹿みたい
Am I an idiot? Like a total fool
見てみたい こっから燃える未来
I want to see the future burning from right here
メラメラ まだまだ自分で決めつけんな限界
Blazing up, don't set limits on yourself just yet
探せお前の視点変え
Search for it, change your perspective
ホントの自分なんていやしねえよ
There's no such thing as your "true self"
高くなきゃダメ 低くてもダメ
It's no good if it's not high, no good if it's low
と思い込んでることこそがダメ
Thinking that way is what's really no good
好きこそものの上手なれ
What you love, you will do well
次こそ吠える根比べ
Next time will be a contest of endurance to roar
I can be so one way, so I know I know
このブレーキを壊したいの したいの
I want to break these brakes, I really do
あー 四の五の言わずに動け
Ah, move without making excuses
道なき道ほど進め
Push forward all the more where there is no path
どの叱咤も嫉妬なら燃料
Any scolding is fuel if it comes from jealousy
Let it fire!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子 ぶち壊し
Burning this fighting spirit, smashing through those iron bars
どうしようもないままが 自分なんだ
Being helpless as I am is who I am
こっから始まんんだ
It starts from right here
いつかの童心持ってたろうし 夢と
I probably had childhood innocence once, and with dreams
相思相愛になれるはずなんだ
We should be able to fall in mutual love
こっから こっから始まんんだ
From here, it starts from right here
Yo! 1 2 3 4 順番通り
Yo! 1 2 3 4, right in order
いってないだけで予定通り
Just haven't said it, but it's all as planned
Rollin' rollin' 転がっていけ
Rollin' rollin', keep on rolling
よりどりみどりの一生
A life full of endless choices
1 2 3 4 順番通り
1 2 3 4, right in order
いってないだけで予定通り
Just haven't said it, but it's all as planned
Rollin' rollin' 転がっていけ
Rollin' rollin', keep on rolling
こっから始まんんだ
It starts from right here
数年後
[A few years later]
Ha-ah, ha-ah...
I can't see what's behind those eyes
Just wait, talk a little before they're right
誰かの理想像に 耳を傾けてしまったの
I ended up listening to someone else's ideal vision
I can't take it back no more, I guess it's too late to call it off
感情の無い世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in an emotionless world
Tell me who I'm supposed to be, I'm lost without your honesty
I'm stuck between yes and no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for 狂ったように舞いな
This is what you came for, dance like you're crazy
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
Show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher
何かを言おうとして 間違い探しのスタート合図
Trying to say something, the signal to start playing spot-the-difference
Why's everybody's eyes on me
慣れてしまうものね 視線の標的
You get used to it, being the target of everyone's gaze
I can't take it back no more, I guess it's too late to call it off
感じるプレッシャーは押し殺してさ
Suppressing the pressure I feel inside
Tell me who I'm supposed to be, I'm lost without your honesty
いい子気取りじゃない no, no, no
I'm not pretending to be a good kid, no, no, no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for 狂ったように舞いな
This is what you came for, dance like you're crazy
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
Show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher
"Said you wanna be a superstar" "So show me what you got"
I can't take it back no more, I guess it's too late to call it off
感情の無い世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in an emotionless world
Tell me who I'm supposed to be, I'm lost without your honesty
I'm stuck between yes and no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for 狂ったように舞いな
This is what you came for, dance like you're crazy
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
Show me you won't break and fall apart
わぁ！みんなー！ありがとう！
Wow! Everyone! Thank you!
仲間と励まし合って
Encouraging each other with my friends,
みんなから勇気をもらって
receiving courage from everyone,
こうしてステージに立って たくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることが出来ました！
I was able to stand on stage like this and perform in front of so many people!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
そして なんと！Xトレンド1位！ありがとうございます！
And... guess what! We hit #1 on X trends! Thank you so much!
そして チャンネル登録者様も 120万人様になったみたいで... 本当にありがとうございます！
And it seems we also reached 1.2 million channel subscribers... Thank you so much!
わぁ！嬉しい！
Wow! I'm so happy!
こうしてね 夢を追いかけて 上京して...
You know, following my dream like this, moving to Tokyo...
たくさんの人のスターになることが出来ました！届け Hajime！
I was able to become a star to so many people! Reach them, Hajime!
ま、でもね この物語を作るにあたって たくさんの素敵なアーティストさんの楽曲をお借りして 作ることが出来ましたので 本当にありがとうございます！
Well, but you know, in creating this story, I was able to use songs from many wonderful artists, so thank you so much!
はじめも 曲をたくさん作れるように頑張ります！
I'll also do my best so that Hajime can make lots of songs!
そして これがはじめの100万人記念の新衣装になります！
And... this is Hajime's 1-million subscriber commemorative new outfit!
衣装の名前は「ブラッドコード」な衣装です 市原タツヤさんに仕立てていただきました！
The outfit is called "Blood Code". Tatsuya Ichihara tailored it for me!
みんなちゃんがね 応援してくれたおかげです！ありがとうございます！
It's all thanks to everyone supporting me! Thank you so much!
で、今回の新衣装ね...
And for this new outfit...
髪がロング！そして 脚がなんか... すごく長く見えるデザインで ほら セクシーなお見せっち！
Long hair! And a design that makes my legs look super long... See, showing off a sexy side!
ちょっとね みんなちゃん なんかおかしくない？ ぴょこぴょこがない！嘘だ！そんなバカな！そんなバカな！
Wait, everyone, isn't something strange? Where are my twintails?! No way! That's impossible! That's impossible!
ぴょこぴょこがないだちょ...
There are no twintails...
うわぁ！嘘です！ぴょこぴょこともあります！
Uwah! Just kidding! The twintails are here too!
ま、ぴょこぴょかないと脳みそ出ちゃうからね 必要だよね！
Well, without the twintails, my brain would spill out, so they're necessary, right?
あと ジャケットも脱げます！ほら！ほら セクシー！
Also, I can take off the jacket! See! Look, sexy!
詳しくはこの後の面談で紹介するので 気になる方は見に来てください！
I'll introduce it in detail during the stream afterwards, so please come watch if you're curious!
えー 続いてなんと！新曲を披露しようと思います！
And next, guess what! I'm going to perform a new song!
皆さん 盛り上がる準備 出来てますかー？！
Everyone, are you ready to get hyped?!
ロング可愛い？ありがとう！
Is long hair cute? Thank you!
とてもね カッコよくて なんかセクシーな感じの曲になっているので ぜひ聴いてください！
It's a really cool and kind of sexy song, so please give it a listen!
それでは行きます！Deep Dive！
Here we go! Deep Dive!
Late night 今夜は with my girlies
Late night, tonight with my girlies
baby すぐ出なよ (Let’s get party, yeah)
Baby come out right now (Let's get party, yeah)
頭からつま先 キメてる lips
Made up lips from head to toe
OK, my ladies I need you to show me
Wow マジ gorgeous, thanks
Wow, seriously gorgeous, thanks
You look so badass
Scream, scream, scream and shout, ay
(Scream, scream, scream and shout)
Wow マジ gorgeous, thanks
Wow, seriously gorgeous, thanks
You look so badass
Scream, scream, scream and shout, ay
Turn it up now, let go
Me and my girls, me and my girls 見てよ
Me and my girls, me and my girls, look at us
Me and my girls, me and my girls ここから
Me and my girls, me and my girls, from right here
We’re amazing, we are so amazing
We're amazing, we are so amazing
Me and my girls, me and my girls 見てよ
Me and my girls, me and my girls, look at us
Me and my girls, me and my girls ここから
Me and my girls, me and my girls, from right here
Dive Yes, I’m a hot queen
Dive, yes, I'm a hot queen
Dive, let’s deep dive, I wanna deep dive
Dive, let's deep dive, I wanna deep dive
Dive, yeah deep dive, ay, ay, ay
Dive, let’s deep dive, I wanna deep dive
Dive, let's deep dive, I wanna deep dive
Dive, yeah deep dive
Let’s get out of control
Let's get out of control
Girl, you like it that, girl, maji you’re so hot
Girl, you like it like that, girl, seriously you're so hot
Burn, まさに queen, hot queen, hot queen
Burn, truly a queen, hot queen, hot queen
Girl, you like it that, girl, maji you’re so hot
Girl, you like it like that, girl, seriously you're so hot
Burn, まさに queen, hot queen, hot queen
Burn, truly a queen, hot queen, hot queen
ワンストロークで star, glow
Star, glow in one stroke
Bare minimum でも hard core
Hard core even with bare minimum
ネイル光って so shiny
Nails shining so shiny
マスカラして I’m burning
Mascara on, I'm burning
髪 down? それとも pony?
Hair down? Or a pony?
Ooh-la-la ooh-la-la
視線を control
Control the gaze
I don’t mind them
I don't mind them
誰かの approval
Someone's approval
I don’t need it no more
I don't need it no more
Wow マジ gorgeous, thanks
Wow, seriously gorgeous, thanks
You look so badass
Give me give me shot, ey
とりあえずな
For now,
Make up!
Are you ready? Are you ready, ready girls?
Me & my girls, me & my girls
We got a, we got a, we got a, we got a
Crazy, crazy
Let's get back to beat 揺さぶる Heart queen
Let's get back to beat, shaking heart queen
Dive, let's deep dive I wanna deep dive Dive, yeah deep dive
Dive, let's deep dive I wanna deep dive Dive, yeah deep dive Let's get it on again
Yeah, look at like that girl マジ超 Hot Heart
Yeah, look at like that girl, seriously super hot heart
まさに Queen, Heart queen, Heart queen
Truly queen, heart queen, heart queen
Yeah, look at like that girl マジ超 Hot Heart
Yeah, look at like that girl, seriously super hot heart
まさに Queen, Heart queen, Heart queen
Truly queen, heart queen, heart queen
はい、ということで！生誕グッズが出ました！
Alright! Birthday merchandise is now available!
怒涛の初っ端、誕生日記念2026のフルセットはこんな感じです！
Right off the bat, here is the Birthday Celebration 2026 Full Set!
1つずつ紹介していきます！
I'll introduce them one by one!
1つ目！ぶんぶんばんちょーアクリルスタンド！
First! The Bunbun Bancho Acrylic Stand!
イラストはA5き先生に描いていただきました！
The illustration was drawn by A5ki-sensei!
台座パーツが2つあるので
Since there are two base parts,
座ってる風にも、空中引っ掛けとしてでも使えます！
you can display it sitting down or hanging in mid-air!
怒っているのがポイントです！
The angry expression is the main point!
2つ目は！はじめとおそろいチョーカー！
Second! The Matching Choker with Hajime!
はじめの新衣装とおそろいのチョーカーです！
It's the same choker Hajime wears with her new outfit!
星のチャームが可愛い！
The star charm is so cute!
首のサイズが合わないよっていう方は、お鞄などにつけてください！
If it doesn't fit your neck, please attach it to your bag!
3つ目は！BANCHOジャージ！
Third! The BANCHO Jersey!
背面のイラストはおもちチャウチャーちゃんに描いていただきました！
The illustration on the back was drawn by Omochi Chowder-chan!
表面は刺繍になってます！
The front features embroidery!
スバル先輩の生地がとても良かったので、同じのにしていただきました！
Subaru-senpai's jersey fabric was great, so I had mine made with the same material!
最後！ぬいぐるみキーホルダー ブラックオーロラ衣装ver.！
Lastly! Plushie Keychain Black Aurora Outfit Ver.!
初めて出した人気のぬいぐるみの新衣装バージョンです！
This is a new outfit version of the popular plushie we released before!
あの時買えなかったよっていう方、ぜひお迎えしてください！
For those who couldn't buy it back then, please welcome it home!
そしてフルセット特典はこちら！
And here is the Full Set bonus!
今回のライブのチケット風カード！
A ticket-style card for this live show!
全員に直筆サイン書かせていただきます！
I'll hand-sign every single one of them!
昨年のライブでたくさんグッズを買っていただいたおかげで
Thanks to everyone buying so much merch at last year's live,
今年もこんなに力を入れることができました！ありがとうございます！
I was able to put this much effort into it again this year! Thank you so much!
今回のライブも楽しんでいただけたら
If you enjoy this live performance as well,
記念にグッズお迎えしていただけると今後の励みになります！
getting the merch as a souvenir will encourage me for the future!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you for your support!
以上、グッズ紹介でした！
That concludes the merch introduction!
はー、しみた！
Phew, that took a lot out of me!
この後ラストパート！
Up next is the final part!
一緒に盛り上がっていってください！いきますよー！
Let me see you all get hyped up together! Here we go!
イエイ！
Yeah!
オウ！
Ow!
イエーイ！ ウオー！ ハイ！
Yeah! Woah! Hey!
ハイ！ ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
みんなー！ ありがとうー！
Everyone! Thank you!
みんな、ありがとうございましたー！
Everyone, thank you so much!
それでは今回のライブに携わってくださった方をご紹介していきたいと思います！
Now, I'd like to introduce the people who were involved in this concert!
まずはダンサー！ ゆめニャー！
First, the dancers! Yume-nya!
で、ちおニャー！
And Chio-nya!
うみニャー！
Umi-nya!
そらー！
Sora!
ありがとう！ そしてこの場には居ないんですけど、振付のMiU / 筋トレ女子先生！
Thank you! And although they aren't here, choreographer MiU / Kintore Joshi-sensei!
タップのAYAKA先生！
Tap dance, AYAKA-sensei!
で、ポッピン、Dodo先生！
And Popping, Dodo-sensei!
ダンス監修、YUKA先生！
Dance supervisor, YUKA-sensei!
ヴォーカル監修、MaRya先生！
Vocal supervisor, MaRya-sensei!
そしてゲストにお越しいただきました！
And we had guest appearances!
星街すいせいちゃん！
Hoshimachi Suisei-chan!
ハコス・ベイルズちゃん！
Hakos Baelz-chan!
伊沙城りおなちゃん！
Izaki Riona-chan!
水宮つうちゃん！
Mizumiya Tsuu-chan!
本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
そして今見えない中で稼働してくださってるスタッフの皆様！
And all the staff members working behind the scenes!
そして配信の目の前に居てくれてる、見てくれた皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
And everyone watching in front of the stream, thank you so much!
それでは、ちょっと新曲について詳しくご紹介したいなと思います！
Now, I'd like to tell you more about my new song!
改めてタイトルは「Deep Dive」！
Once again, the title is "Deep Dive"!
はい！ MV公開、この配信のすぐ後です！
Yes! The MV release is right after this stream!
音源配信は本日24時からになります！
The audio release will be today from 24:00!
皆さんたくさん聴いていただけると嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy if everyone listens to it a lot!
さあ！ それではここで！
Now then, right here!
重大発表いきたいと思います！ こちらの動画をご覧ください！
I have a major announcement! Please take a look at this video!
一条莉々華 × FILA コラボ決定!!
[Ichijou Ririka × FILA Collaboration Confirmed!!]
わー！ すごい！ この度一条とFILAちゃんのコラボが決定しましたー！
Wow! Amazing! A collaboration between Ichijou and FILA has been confirmed!
うわー嬉しい！ ありがとうございます！
Uwa, I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
そしてなんと、スニーカーを含むアパレルをプロデュースさせていただきました！
And amazingly, I got to produce apparel including sneakers!
やったー！
Yay!
一条っぽいカラーリングを取り入れながら、男性でも女性でも似合うように意識してデザインいたしました！
While incorporating Ichijou-style coloring, I designed them so they'd suit both men and women!
一生懸命一条のこだわりを詰め込んだスニーカーになっていくので、続報を楽しみに待っていてください！
I'm packing all of Ichijou's dedication into these sneakers, so please look forward to further updates!
そして今回なんとスニーカーだけじゃなくてね、ジャージとTシャツと、あ、キャップもプロデュースしましたー！
And this time, not just sneakers, but I also produced tracksuits, T-shirts, and caps!
さらにコラボにあたって、オリジナルのコラボロゴをFILAさんと作りました！ ドドン！
Furthermore, for this collab, we created an original collaboration logo with FILA! Ta-da!
わー可愛い！
Wow, so cute!
実はこのね、ロゴ、FILAさんと一緒に打ち合わせをして、あの、考えました、一条。
Actually, I had meetings with FILA and came up with this logo myself.
あ、こういう感じでね、実際に手書きをしながら打ち合わせをして...
Ah, like this, we had meetings while making hand drawings...
どの色がいいかなって、いろんな色味を出してもらって作りました。
Thinking about which color would be best, they showed me various shades to make this.
ひと目でね、こう一条だって分かる、こうミニ番長のシルエットが良いかなと思って入れてみました！
I thought it'd be great to include mini-Bancho's silhouette so you can tell at a glance that it's Ichijou!
このロゴがね、コラボの商品にも付きます！ 楽しみですねー！
This logo will also be on the collaboration items! Isn't that exciting?!
実はね、アパレル以外にもFILAさんとのコラボ商品が出ますので、皆さん詳細な情報が出るのをぜひお楽しみに、お待ちください！
Actually, there will be other collaboration products with FILA besides apparel, so please look forward to the details!
えーこの後はですね、メン限でアンコールライブ、21時15分からありますし！
Um, after this, there's a members-only encore live starting from 21:15!
この新曲についても色々詳しく見ていければと思いますので...
And I'd also like to look into this new song in detail...
ぜひまだの方はチャンネル登録と通知をオンにして、メン限配信に来ていただけると、アンコールも一緒に楽しめてハッピーだなと思います！
So if you haven't yet, please subscribe and turn on notifications, and if you come to the members-only stream, we can enjoy the encore together!
おさらいをすると...
To summarize...
新曲MV、この後すぐ公開！
New song MV released right after this!
21時からグッズ販売！
Goods sales starting from 21:00!
21時15分からアンコールライブ！
Encore live from 21:15!
24時、新曲音源リリースです！
24:00, new song audio release!
ありがとうねー！
Thank you everyone!
それでは！ メン限アンコールライブでお会いしましょう！ バイバーイ！
Well then! See you at the members-only encore live! Bye-bye!
いっぱいコメントありがとう！ 嬉しかったー！
Thank you for all the comments! I was so happy!
あ、ありがとう！
Ah, thank you!